josephprince.org 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Joseph Prince Ministries

At Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc., we respect, and will do our best to protect, the privacy of anyone who provides us with any personally identifiable information or PII. PII is defined as any information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact or locate a person, such as name, address, contact number(s), and email addresses.

In this privacy policy, we set out the practices we abide by as a ministry to protect your PII. This policy also applies to our online store. Please read through this privacy policy before you use our website because by using our website, you are automatically agreeing with the points covered here. If you do not agree with them, we would advise you not to use our website.

### YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION: WHAT WE COLLECT, AND HOW WE USE IT

We do not collect PII about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us. During your visit, if you browse through our website, read pages, or download information, the web server will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally. We may use such information or any information you choose to provide to monitor our website’s performance, and to make improvements where necessary.

### INFORMATION STORED AUTOMATICALLY

By default, all web server log files capture Internet Provider (IP) addresses. We may use your IP address internally to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website and to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or cause damage.

A cookie is a small amount of information sent from a web server to your computer. We use cookies when someone logs onto our website to maintain that login, to retain login information (if requested) and for the maintenance of our online store cart service. Any activity you engage in while you are at the Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc. website may be tracked. We do not use cookies to track your Internet activity before you enter or after you leave our website.

### THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

If you are a registered user, you are required to provide your email address and password when you login to our website.

If you belong to a subscription program or any other program under Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc., we may ask for information which identifies you as a program member.

When you place an online order or make an online donation, you will be required to provide your name, email address, mailing address, contact number, payment card details and/or other information (e.g. special delivery instructions). We may share selected information with our agents, sub-contractors (e.g. shipping company) and/or third parties (e.g. the issuer of your payment card) for the sole purpose of delivering the product(s) you requested or processing your donation.

When you participate in any contest or promotion, we may ask for your name, address, email address and/or other information so we can administer the contest/promotion and notify winners.

If you choose to provide us with any PII by sending an email to Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc., or by filling out a form with your PII and submitting it through our website, we may use that information to provide the information, service(s) and/or product(s) you have requested or to minister to you.

We do not collect PII for other purposes. The information you provide is not released to any third party for commercial marketing and gains or otherwise, without your permission except where required by law to do so (such as in the investigation of fraud or other inappropriate activity).

### ACCESS TO AND UPDATING OF INFORMATION

We endeavor to maintain the accuracy of your PII and rely on you to ensure it is complete and accurate. You may verify, correct, or remove your PII through your website-specific registration, through your profile, or by contacting us with a request for change. We may take steps to verify your identity before making changes to your PII.

### HOW WE RESPOND TO "DO NOT TRACK" SIGNALS

California Law requires us to disclose how we respond to "Do Not Track" signals. At this time, we do not respond to browser ‘Do Not Track’ signals.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our activities are not directed to individuals under 13. We do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with PII, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with PII, please contact us.

### EMAILS FROM JOSEPH PRINCE MINISTRIES, INC.

Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc. has found that attractive, graphics-rich emails are a quick and effective way to inform our registered users and subscribers of new resources, clearance and sale items, projects and events to provide them opportunities to support our ministry. We maintain an opt-out, user-customizable subscription database of users who have requested to receive these emails. Every email provides an option for you to unsubscribe to such information.

### SECURITY

To make online giving and shopping at the Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc. website a safe and secure experience, we use a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) capable browser. This means that any credit/debit card information you send is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our server, making it extremely difficult for others to access your private information during transmission.

While we will make reasonable efforts to store any PII which we hold in a secure server or in secure files, and to keep this information accurate and up-to-date, the Internet is not a secure medium for the transmission of information. Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc. cannot accept responsibility for the security of information you send to or receive from us over the Internet or for any unauthorized access to or use of that information.

Unauthorized attempts to upload information to or change information on our website are strictly prohibited and may be punishable by law.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites. Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of these other websites. Should you choose to follow a link to another website, you are subject to its privacy policy.

### VARIATION

Joseph Prince Ministries, Inc. may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to visit our website regularly to stay updated of these changes as your continued use of our website indicates your acceptance of these changes.

### FUTURE CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We regularly review this Privacy Policy and may change, modify, add, or remove portions as needed. If we change this Privacy Policy in ways that affect how we use your PII, we will notify you here or in a notice on our home page. We will also update the revision date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time to remain informed of any changes.

### EFFECTIVE DATE

This version of the Privacy Policy became effective on 19 June 2017.
